Contact

03004654333 (Mobile) ranawaleedmanzoor@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/ranawaleed (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

C#

.NET Framework
Transact-SQL (T-SQL)

Languages

Punjabi (Native or Bilingual)
Urdu (Native or Bilingual)
English (Professional Working)

Certifications

English for Career Development Scrum Foundation Professional Certificate (SFPC)

Honors-Awards

Best Ambassador of Fall 2016
Best Ambassador of Spring 2017
Campus Gold Medal
Institute Silver Medal

Waleed Manzoor

Team Lead | Software Engineer | ASP.NET | Angular | JavaScript Pakistan

Summary

Software Engineer with 5 years of demonstrated history of working in the software industry. Skilled in .NET, .NET Core, Angular and Odoo. My strongest soft-skill areas are presentation, people management, team player & learning flexibility.

Experience

NAGC Lahore Senior Software Engineer August 2020 - Present (1 year 6 months)

MTBC

2 years 7 months

Lead Software Engineer
June 2019 - August 2020 (1 year 3 months)
Northern Punjab Rawalpindi, Pakistan

- -Leading a Dev Team of 10 people
- -Collaborated with the team to refactor the code and reduce the service loading time by 95%
- -Servers Monitoring, Sprint Management, Release Management, and Code Reviews

Software Engineer

February 2018 - June 2019 (1 year 5 months)

Northern Punjab Rawalpindi, Pakistan

Working on Angular 4 and MVC 5. Developed different modules of the company's main streamline product e.g. SignalR implementation, Document Manager, Schedulers, Rights Authorization. Also providing live support to clients by analyzing statements, debug issues and develop the generic solution.

DigitalNet Technology Solutions Software Engineer | Odoo Developer July 2017 - January 2018 (7 months)

Lahore, Pakistan

- -Worked on Odoo 10.0. Having full command on customized security groups, record rules, models, views, actions, menus, modules integration, and Odoo deployment. Developed Following ERP projects:
- -E-Purchasing -Meeting Point -E-leave Management

Plan9 - PITB's Tech Incubator Internee Software Engineer June 2016 - August 2016 (3 months) Arfa Software Technology Park, Lahore

As an internee software engineer, I developed 3 major projects for the company listed as follows:

- Cargo Management System for DCS Pakistan
- Construction Estimator Application
- · Hospital Management System

Education

National University of Sciences and Technology (NUST) Master of Science - MS, Computer Science · (2018 - 2020)

COMSATS University

Bachelor's Degree, Software Engineering · (2013 - 2017)